(Sheldon(entering):)Well, you can add Jerry's Junction
to the Iist of train stores...
(Sheldon(entering):)...Sheldon Cooper
will never set foot in again.
- Rough night, Casey Jones?
- You don't know the haIf of it.
(Sheldon:)It was billed as a lively give-and-take
on the merits of model-train sizes.
(Sheldon:)But it was actually a set-up...
(Sheldon:)...to intimidate weak-minded, spineless
rubes into buying HO starter sets.
- What's in the bag?
- I don't wanna talk about it.
But it's not a spine, I'll tell you that.
(Amy:)I had a delightful evening.
We should do this again sometime.
Uh, sure. That'd be nice.
(Amy:)Glad to hear it. I need someone
to accompany me to the wedding...
(Amy:)...of Dr. Moranelli and Dr. Gustufson
this Friday.
(Amy:)They're kind of the Brad and Angelina
of the Primatology Department.
- Wouldn't you rather bring Sheldon?
- I would...
(Amy:)...but the last wedding we went to
was a disaster.
(Amy:)- He behaved like a child the entire time.
- It's not my fauIt.
(Sheldon:)You said there'd be other scientists there
my age.